<?xml version="1.0"?>
<MenuItems>
    <MenuItem id="setupPowerOnCommands">
        <Name>Setup TV for Network-On</Name>
        <CallbackMethod>enable_power_on_commands</CallbackMethod>
        <ButtonTitle>Run</ButtonTitle>
        <ConfigUI>
			<Field id="instructions" type="label" fontSize="small">
				<Label>In order for your TV to respond to a "Power On" command while in standby mode, we must enable this feature. According to Sharp, power consumption is not significantly increased, but the power light will remain glowing when the TV screen is off in order to indicate it is in standby mode.
				</Label>
			</Field>
			<Field id="targetTVs" type="list">
				<Label>TV:</Label>
				<List class="indigo.devices" filter="self" /> 
			</Field>
			<Field id="powerOnInstructions" type="label" fontSize="small" alignWithControl="true">
				<Label>Please make sure your TV(s) are powered on and connected before running this command; otherwise the command may fail. Once this is executed you may check the success by turning the TV off and looking for the power light to remain green after the picture has turned off.</Label>
			</Field>
        </ConfigUI>
    </MenuItem>
    <MenuItem id="sendNonDocumentedCommand">
		<Name>Send Arbitrary Command</Name>
		<CallbackMethod>send_arbitrary_command</CallbackMethod>
		<ButtonTitle>Send</ButtonTitle>
		<ConfigUI>
			<Field id="sendArbitraryCommandTitle" type="label" fontColor="darkGray">
				<Label>SEND ARBITRARY COMMAND</Label>
			</Field>
			<Field id="titleSeparator" type="separator" />
			<Field type="label" id="commandSendInstructions" fontSize="small">
				<Label>This allows sending an arbitrary command to the Sharp television for use in debugging control codes. The code will be sent just as if from the other actions, but with any value typed here.</Label>
			</Field>
			<Field id="targetDevice" type="menu">
				<Label>Receiver:</Label>
				<List class="indigo.devices" filter="self.sharpTvRemoteDevice" /> 
			</Field>
			<Field type="textfield" id="commandToSend">
				<Label>Command:</Label>
			</Field>
			<Field id="exampleCommandFormat" type="label" fontSize="small" alignWithControl="true">
				<Label>Example Commands: POWR? or WIDE4</Label>
			</Field>
		</ConfigUI>
	</MenuItem>

    <MenuItem id="deviceCmdsSeparator" />
    <MenuItem id="toggleDebug">
		<Name>Toggle Debugging On/Off</Name>
		<CallbackMethod>toggle_debug_enabled</CallbackMethod>
	</MenuItem>
	<MenuItem id="debugDumpDeviceDetails">
		<Name>Log Device Details</Name>
		<CallbackMethod>dump_device_details_to_log</CallbackMethod>
		<ButtonTitle>Output</ButtonTitle>
		<ConfigUI>
			<Field id="dumpDeviceDetailsToLog_Title" type="label" fontColor="darkGray">
				<Label>DEVICE DETAILS DEBUG</Label>
			</Field>
			<Field id="dumpDeviceDetailsToLog_TitleSeparator" type="separator" />
			<Field type="label" id="dumpDeviceDetailsToLogInstructions" fontSize="small">
				<Label>This function will dump the details of a plugin device to the Indigo Event Log to aid in debugging and forum posts.</Label>
			</Field>
			<Field id="devicesToDump" type="list">
				<Label>Devices to Log:</Label>
				<List class="indigo.devices" filter="self" />
			</Field>
		</ConfigUI>
	</MenuItem>
	
	<MenuItem id="updateSectionSeparator" />
	<MenuItem id="viewLicense">
		<Name>View License...</Name>
		<ConfigUI>
			<Field id="licenseText" type="label" fontSize="small">
				<Label>MIT License

Copyright (c) [2013 - Present] [Adam A. (@RogueProeliator)]

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.
				</Label>
			</Field>
		</ConfigUI>
	</MenuItem>
</MenuItems>